I visited the orphanage today.
I go every month, remember?
The children are so cute.
If I have a child,
maybe I'll raise her there.
Show her the flowers and trees.
Plus, it's close to Seoul.
Uh? The tow truck?
They said it might take a while.
I love hearing your voice now.
It feels romantic
to hear your voice in the snow.
Does your tyre have an air leak?
Yes. I called for a tow truck.
It'll take a long time
to get here since it's snowing.
Hold on.
Let me take a look.
I said it's okay,
but he's looking at it.
Really?
I think you should just wait
for the tow truck.
No, it's not hard
to change a flat tyre.
But why bother
when a tow truck's coming?
Hold on a sec.
Status?
OK.
Hello? Ju-yeon?
I'd better get going.
Lock the doors
and just wait for the tow truck.
Wait.
My love
Is so sweet
Like a mother's...
The tow truck's on its way.
Why's he bothering?
There are too many people around here.
Sorry to be working
on your birthday again.
I'll be home soon.
Your car's completely sunk.
Thank you, but I'll just wait
for the tow truck.
Thank you so much
CHILD SAFE VEHICLE
Why isn't he leaving?
I SAW THE DEVIL
Mister...
Mister?
It's going to be easy
since your skin is so soft.
Please don't kill me.
Why?
I'm...
I'm pregnant.
Spare my life, please.
Dong-su! Dong-su!
- What?
- Come over here! Hurry Up!
Chief, why did you come out here?
We'll keep you posted at home.
What happened?
What happened to my daughter?
Don't look. Not now.
Nothing's for sure yet.
- Detective Cho?
- What?
- Here.
- What? Let me see.
It looks like hair. Flip it over.
Forensics! Come here quick!
We found the head!
Look after Chief Jang!
Stop taking pictures!
Block them off!
Still, heaven helped us.
Otherwise,
we wouldn't have found her.
How ironic.
I was a police detective
for over 30 years.
And couldn't even protect
my own daughter.
Please stop smoking, sir.
I'm sorry.
I'm...
I'm really sorry.
To you...
...and to Ju-yeon...
I am so sorry.
Forgive me, Ju-yeon.
I wasn't there for you.
Always late...
And never there for you.
But Ju-yeon...
...I promise you this...
...I'll make him pay for your pain.
I'll make him pay.
Soo-hyun...
So how long do you want?
Nothing's urgent.
Do you want a couple of months off?
- Two weeks is enough, sir.
- You can take more.
No, I'll come back to work
in two weeks, sir
Well, I'd really appreciate that.
Are you sure?
Very well. Then I'll be
expecting you in two weeks.
In the meantime, please rest.
I can't believe this happened.
Didn't they get engaged
just last month?
I can't quite believe it.
Hi.
Here's the GPS.
And the capsule.
With embedded GPS
and microphone. Smart, isn't it?
Well done.
Thank you.
Not at all.
- Aren't you going back?
- Eh?
- Anything else to tell me?
- No.
Well, as you know,
I snuck this out.
So if something goes wrong,
you and I will...
Don't worry.
Nothing will go wrong.
It looks like the police...
...think these four are
the main suspects.
They've been accused
on similar cases before.
- Hi, Soo-hyun.
- Hi.
Have you had supper?
I'd better get going.
I bought some groceries for dad.
I'll be going then.
Take care, sir.
- Are you leaving?
- Yeah.
Why isn't this bastard budging?
Yes?
No suspicious moves yet.
Yes, sir.
This bastard's the sickest one.
Remember this?
You really don't know?
I see...
What the fuck is with him?
Why's he turning himself in?
Says he killed the girl found
at Bangho Creek two months ago.
And the missing Shinchon girl case
a few years back.
So he suddenly grew a conscience?
What's with the bruises?
Did you guys do it?
No.
An ambulance came
so I ran up to see,
and this bastard was
practically dying.
What the fuck happened?
Well, he hasn't say anything yet.
What the hell happened last night?
Help me... please
- Help me...
- What's he saying?
Some bastard hammered his balls.
What? That's insane.
Who bust your balls?
Who the fuck are you?
You motherfucker!
The buses have stopped running.
Where are you going?
- Pardon me?
- I said, where are you going?
- To the Sung-min Apartments.
- Sung-min?
Well, it's kind of on the way. Hop in.
- I'll give you a ride.
- No thanks.
I'll give you a ride. Get in.
I'm fine.
Sung-min Apartments are
just down the road. Hop in.
It's all right.
Are you sure?
Yeah, it's fine. Get in.
- What?
- Yes? Oh, nothing.
Is this a school bus?
Ah, shit. Where did I put it?
What?
Yes?
Why do you look like
you stepped on shit?
Never seen one of these before?
Who are you?
Why do you need this
for the insurance money?
I have to identify
the policy holder.
There are too many people
with the same name.
These are all old pictures.
Perhaps this one will do.
I need to ask a few more
standard questions.
Do you have additional
contact numbers for him?
I don't.
But his son does.
Sang-won! Sang-won!
Where's he got to?
I think it was Yang-pyung
or Chung-pyung...
Can you verify that your son is
the man is the man I'm looking for?
Is this Mr Kyung-chul Jang?
It's Kyung-chul all right.
Was this picture taken recently?
How come he looks so scary?
Insurance, my ass!
He doesn't give a shit
about anyone.
He abandoned his parents
and his son.
Like he'd take out
a family insurance?
That doesn't make any sense!
- Don't talk like that!
- Am I wrong?
- There's no use protecting him!
- Shut up!
- He's good for nothing!
- Please shut your mouth!
- Don't get me started!
- Why are you saying that?
- Don't say stuff like that.
- Oh, fuck it!
By the way, doesn't the family get
the money if the policy holder dies?
Does his family get the money?
Are you Sang-won?
Do you know where
your father lives now?
Shit.
Why?
She's a really good singer.
- Maybe I can go.
- Of course you'll go.
Mum's going to kill me.
Don't go anywhere but home now.
All right?
Yes, Miss.
Driver, please don't let them
out elsewhere.
- Of course.
- Thank you.
- Can I help you?
- Is Kyung-chul Jang here?
- Why? Is there a problem?
- We're the police. Where is he?
- He's driving some pupils home now.
- Shit! Call his mobile, now! Hurry!
LEARNING CENTRE
What? One girl is missing?
How could the fools on stakeout
miss him driving the girls out?
Were you sleeping on the stakeout?
Stop talking shit!
Shit happens?
Did any of you watch the back door?
Did you plan to catch him
after saying hello, you fuckwits?
Listen to me.
Locate the van first.
And find him no matter what!
Forget the fucking warrant!
Just snatch him first!
Jang's the murderer.
Get him no matter what!
It's me.
I came home to change but
I haven't got time now. Turn the car...
- Where are you going?
- My friend's.
- Who?
- Like you know my friends!
- Did you come to change clothes?
- Give me clothes, I don't have time.
I wasn't talking to you.
- Why are you going out at this time?
- To study!
- Why are you studying there?
- Stop nagging me!
Are you answering me back?
Come here!
- No!
- Just you...
What are you doing now?
Hurry up.
Don't cry like a baby
Don't cry...
Now, let me see.
Ah, your skin is so pale.
It's all right.
It'll all be over quickly.
Looks like I won't be driving
the fucking school bus anymore!
Things are fucked up now.
But shit...
...who says I can't like you?
What's wrong with that?
I can like you, can't I?
Why does every bitch in this world
give me so much shit?
Why is that?
It'll all be over soon enough!
Kyung-chul Jang...
What? Are you alone?
Are you a cop?
I must be right.
The cops found me this quick?
I'm surprised.
I guess you don't know
who you're dealing with.
But what can you expect
from the fucking cops?
Anyway...
You son of a bitch!
Fuck you!
What... what the hell is this guy?
This guy's a fucking psycho.
Fucking asshole.
Hello, sir.
Don't know where you're headed,
but you can hop in.
You don't want a ride?
There won't be other cars.
What are you doing
all the way out here alone?
You're pretty lucky, Mister,
catching a cab out here.
It's on the way
for the man in the back.
- You don't mind, right?
- Of course not.
It must've been hard
to get a cab here.
Cars hardly ever go by here.
I don't come here much.
Only once in a while for work.
But today's your lucky day, Mister.
You know that?
Strange things have been
happening around here,
so no one's out at night.
But today I have two customers!
Come to think of it,
it's also my lucky day.
Isn't that right, sir?
Way out here
in the dark of the night.
What's so funny?
Something good happen to you?
- Mister...
- Yes?
You said we're all lucky today.
That's what I said. Why?
But the way I see it,
it's an unlucky day for you.
Crazy bastards.
You're young. It'll heal fast.
Don't worry about it.
And soccer...
You shouldn't play so roughly.
Who plays soccer with their wrists?
Anyway, from now on
take it easy, understand?
We're finished. You can leave.
Hey, you motherfucker.
I ain't your son.
So watch the way you talk to me.
Take off your glasses.
Come here.
Come over here.
Sir, you can come outside now
for your prescription.
How old are you?
I'm 22.
Oh, nice being 22.
Boyfriend?
Eh?
Bet you have plenty of boyfriends.
Right?
No. I don't have any.
Don't fucking lie to me.
A pretty girl like you
without a boyfriend?
You don't know how to do it?
If you don't know,
then you don't know.
I was about to have
a good time last night.
But some bastard turned up
and ruined everything.
So this time...
...let's make this easy.
Take off your clothes.
And do try and enjoy it.
Strip off.
Strip before I cut up
your face, bitch!
Strip now! Bitch!
That's right.
Take off your bra too. Hurry up.
Please...
Good.
Take off your skirt.
You son of a bitch.
Who the fuck are you?
Wait.
Stay here.
He'll need to get treated.
Don't act so weak.
This is just the beginning.
Remember this...
Your nightmare's
only going to get worse.
Look away, Miss.
Look away and plug your ears.
Fuck you, crazy motherfucker!
Son of a bitch!
So you wanna fight me, huh?
You really want to do this,
motherfucker?
Crazy motherfucker.
Fine! Let's see who ends up
eating shit! You bastard!
What is it?
Has there been an accident?
Something's wrong with his car.
Yes, sir.
Is everything OK with you?
I'm just worried about you,
that's all.
The police think
I'm chasing after Jang.
Seems like they're after him, too.
So I was wondering...
...if you could stop chasing him now.
- But I...
- You've done enough.
I want you to stop.
But, sir...
Forget it.
I'll talk to you later.
It's me.
- Soo-hyun.
- Yeah, how are you doing?
Good. How are you?
Well, just busy
working on something.
Really? What kind of work?
You know what I do.
I know what you do normally,
but not what you do secretly.
Dad gave you the police files,
right?
Soo-hyun...
I know how you feel,
but I want you to stop.
Nothing you do
will bring my sister back.
Whatever you do to punish him,
it won't change anything.
Revenge is for the movies.
That bastard's a psycho.
Sorry. I have nothing
to say to you.
What do you mean?
Am I nobody to you?
Do you know how I have been recently?
I keep looking behind me
to check I'm not being followed.
And you have nothing to say?
So... I'm begging you now.
This is meaningless.
Please stop it.
Sorry, I have to go.
And this work is not meaningless.
Soo-hyun? Soo-hyun?
Water. Give me water.
Remember the first time we met?
We tried to form a terrorist group
to fuck the world up!
I really miss those days.
We weren't afraid of anything.
Cut the bullshit
and give me a smoke.
Must be a family member
of a bitch you killed.
Who else would do that?
He's our kind.
He's enjoying the excitement
of going out on a hunt.
Catching and releasing the prey.
Catching and releasing.
He's playing the hunter.
Man...
Looks like you've screwed up bad
this time.
The bastard must've gone crazy
after losing his bitch.
Advent of a monster.
How interesting.
Get some rest.
We got plenty of rooms.
You can sleep in any room.
And I'll go and prepare breakfast
for tomorrow.
Fucking bastards.
Let go of me!
Fuck you.
Shit, you guys are fucking crazy.
Little harder.
Harder.
He's enjoying the excitement
of going out on a hunt.
Catching and releasing the prey.
Catching and releasing.
He's enjoying the excitement
of going out on a hunt.
He's playing the hunter now.
Your nightmare's
only going to get worse.
Amusing...
Come on.
Didn't you see your sister last night?
If you fight it,
it'll only be more painful for you.
It'll all be over quickly.
So just bear with me.
Then why did you suspect us?
Did we ask you for a house
or for money?
We only wanted to stay a few days,
but you gave us shit!
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
You should've apologised
a long time ago.
Damn bitches.
Always acting up when it's too late!
Hold on. The order is arms,
legs and head. Right?
Close your eyes. Best not to look.
Where is she?
How did you get in
without making a noise?
I'm pregnant.
I was wondering
what you'd look like.
You don't look like a monster.
Crazy bastard.
Arms, legs and head, right?
Exactly as you'd do it.
Nothing more, nothing less.
You crazy, psycho fucker.
I'm actually relieved now.
I was worried something
might've happened to you.
He's Soo-hyun Kim
from National Intelligence, right?
Do you want to see
what he's been up to?
Please make him stop.
You can't become a monster
to fight against a monster.
You know it's wrong.
Where is he now?
Your wounds are treated.
You'll get around all right.
You and he slept
for two days straight.
What happened?
Sir?
Just hand the bastard over.
Not yet.
What are you going to do?
You know...
It feels like a huge rock
is pressing down on my chest.
The weight...
I promised Ju-yeon
I'd make him feel the same pain.
It's not over.
Far from it.
All right. No more questions.
So, the capsule's working well?
Unless he has diarrhea...
Don't worry.
The bastard's completely out.
He'll be out
for another day at least.
You know, you changed a lot, sir?
Hello.
Pain killers please.
With dexibuprofen.
What? Dexi what?
- Just give me the strongest kind.
- Very well.
Where are you now?
Guess you're not around.
Hey, are you listening?
Of course you are.
It's been a total blast!
Never had such fun
before in my life.
I know who you are.
Your bitch was Ju-yeon?
From Yeonyi County, right?
You hear me?
But you made a mistake.
You underestimated me.
You'll regret not killing me
when you had the chance.
I'll get you soon.
Hello.
You'll see.
I'll teach you what real pain is.
What are you doing? Hey, you!
By the way...
...before I killed her,
she told me she was pregnant.
She begged for her life.
Did you know that?
Hurry up, asshole.
Otherwise, the man will die.
Should keep close-range
when hunting me.
Kyung-chul Jang,
where did you go?
Do we have to go through all this
to save bastards like them?
Seeing scum like them
makes me sorry to be human.
Call me when they wake up.
What is it this time?
What is it?
What?
Are you sure?
OK.
Hey... Kyung-chul Jang
is turning himself in.
You made a mistake,
you son of a bitch.
Wake up.
I have a question.
Where would your friend go?
You've aggravated the wrong guy.
He always gets even.
Do you know what that means?
Your girl, your girl's family.
When he's done,
he'll give himself up to the police.
But...
...your woman didn't have it
all that bad.
Unlike me,
he likes to give pleasure
before he gives pain!
He gives pleasure first!
Funny?
Is that funny?
That really amuses you?
All right, I'll make you smile
for the rest of your life!
I traced a call from Jang.
I was tapping the police
investigating Jang.
Jang just called them and said
he'd turn himself in today.
But before that, he has some
unfinished business.
Is he going to kill again?
- What's his location?
- Yeonyi County.
Parcel delivery!
Captain Oh?
This is Soo-hyun Kim.
What?
What the hell have you done?
If something happens to him,
I'll kill you! You got that?
Fucking answer me!
Send the nearest men
to the Chief's house now!
Turn around!
Not much resemblance.
No.
Ju-yeon must've taken
after her mother.
Good thing
she didn't look like you.
Why'd you come at me like that,
you old bastard?
Are you crazy?
Let me see.
Shit, where is it?
What would make
that motherfucker get angry?
Would he get mad if I do this?
Like this?
Like this? Like this?
Like this, crazy motherfucker?
Like this, you son of a bitch?
Dad?
I'm home.
- You can't come inside.
- Stay back.
What is it?
Let go of him.
Are you Soo-hyun Kim?
You bastard! Come here!
Have you any idea what you've done?
How dare you show up here!
You piece of shit!
Let go. Let go of me!
You son of a bitch.
Out of the way.
Out of the way!
Hello?
This is Kyung-chul Jang.
Bastard!
Where the hell are you?
You haven't done anything
to Se-yeon?
You'll find out later.
Here.
Hello.
So how does it feel?
You shouldn't have fucked with me,
you piece of shit!
Who do you think has won?
Have you won or have I won?
It's Kyung-chul Jang!
- It's Jang, sir!
- Wait for my command.
Now!
Fast!
Get him! Get him!
Get him!
You were right.
I made a mistake.
I underestimated you.
I'll treat you right from now on.
What are you doing,
you son of a bitch?
This is just the beginning.
You son of a bitch!
Just kill me, you fucker.
Just kill me!
You fuck! Kill me, you bastard!
Hurry up and kill me.
You bastard!
Not just yet. Just a little longer.
If it was that easy,
I would've killed you already.
I'll kill you
at your most painful moment.
When you're trembling
in the utmost pain and fear,
I'll kill you then.
Because only that will be
real revenge.
True revenge.
Spare...
Spare my life.
Let me live... please.
Let me live.
You heard that a lot, right?
"Let me live."
You must've enjoyed hearing that.
Let me live.
Please.
I'll pay for my sins.
So please let me go.
You've done enough.
Please... don't kill me.
I'm sorry.
Please, please spare my life.
I beg you.
I beg you, spare my life.
Are you afraid?
Tell me. Are you afraid?
Do you realise
what you've done now?
Stop fucking around with me.
You fucking son of a bitch.
Stop talking bullshit now.
You've already lost.
You think you got to me?
Fuck you.
Pain? I don't know what pain is.
Fear? I don't know that, either.
There's nothing
you can get out of me.
So... you've lost already.
Got that?
I hope that...
...you suffer even after you die.
Son of a bitch!
You hear me?
It's not over!
I'll live no matter what!
I'll stay alive, you son of a bitch!
Can you hear me?
Eh? Are you listening to me?
I'm afraid of nothing!
You think you can fuck with me?
Dad?
Dad!
Hey!
Hey, don't open the door!
Dad?
No, no, don't open the door!
No! Don't open the door,
Sang-won!
What the hell is he saying?
Don't open it.
It's stuck.
No, no!
What the fuck are you doing here?
- Mum!
- Are you in there?
No. Don't open the door!
Don't open the door!
Get the fuck away!
Kyung-chul!